isekaiscan.com 2019-10-28

# Privacy Policy – Read manga online in english, you can also read manhua, manhwa in english for free. Tons of Isekai manga, manhua and manhwa are available.

We take the privacy of our visitors with utmost care.

We are committed to ensuring that the privacy of the visitors is protected. If we ask for any information from the visitors then we will make sure to use them only in accordance with the privacy statements mentioned below.

* * *

###  What we collect

We may collect name, email, and any other contact information.

* * *

###  What we do with the information we gather

The information we collect is to ensure that the users have the highest opportunity to make use of our website. By providing us with the information the users may log in to their account, comment, subscribe, etc. We do not sell any of the information provided to us by the users.

* * *

###  How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file placed on your computer’s hard drive which helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. Third parties such as our advertisers may also place cookies on your browser in the course of serving ads to you based on your visit to our site and other sites on the internet. If you want to opt out of our third-party advertiser (Google Adsense)’s use of cookies, please visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

* * *

### Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

Google Adsense ads may be served by Google. Google cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy, please contact us using the contact page: Contact us.
